Guide to the J. E. Wallace Sterling, President of Stanford University, Papers
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Series 1
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Hospital, 1965-1966 (Box A22, Folder 23)
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Hospital, 1959-1960 (Box A22, Folder 24)
    Dr. Barnett, Director
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Hospital, 1956-1958 (Box A22, Folder 25)
    Board of Directors
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Hospital, 1959-1963 (Box A22, Folder 26)
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Hospital, 1963-1966 (Box A22, Folder 27)
    Board of Directors, Joint Owners Committee
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Hospital, 1955-1956 (Box A22, Folder 28)
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Hospital, 1957-1959 (Box A22, Folder 29)
    Director, Dr. Barnett
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Hospital, 1957-1959 (Box A22, Folder 30)
    Administrative Expenditures
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Hospital, 1958-1959 (Box A22, Folder 31)
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Hospital, 1958-1959 (Box A22, Folder 32)
    Organization Committee, Frank W. Piersol
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Hospital, 1956-1957 (Box A22, Folder 33)
    Steering Committee
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Medical Center, 1955-1959 (Box A23, Folder 1)
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Medical Center, 1959 (Box A23, Folder 2)
    Dedication invitation lists
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Medical Center, 1959 (Box A23, Folder 3)
    Dedication - misc. letters
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Medical Center, 1959 (Box A23, Folder 4)
    Dedication planning
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Medical Center, 1959 (Box A23, Folder 5)
    Dedication publicity
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Medical Center, 1956-1957 (Box A23, Folder 6)
    Public Information Committee
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Medical Center, 1959 (Box A23, Folder 7)
    Dedication - speaker, speeches
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Medical Center, 1957-1958 (Box A23, Folder 8)
    Fund
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Medical Center, 1956-1957 (Box A23, Folder 9)
    Fund - Corporate Gifts Committee
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Medical Center, 1956-1957 (Box A23, Folder 10)
    Fund - Management Committee
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Medical Center, 1957 (Box A23, Folder 11)
    Fund - Medical Alumni Committee
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Medical Center, 1956-1958 (Box A23, Folder 12)
    Fund - Personal Gifts Committee
  - Palo Alto - Stanford Medical Center, 1956-1957 (Box A23, Folder 13)
    Groundbreaking
  - Memorial Church and Religion, 1946-1950 (Box A23, Folder 14)
  - Palo Alto Unified School District, 1955-1958 (Box A23, Folder 15)
  - Palo Alto Vehicle Safety Check, 1957 (Box A23, Folder 16)
  - Palo Alto Times, 1956-1964 (Box A23, Folder 17)
  - Panel of Americans, 1957-1961 (Box A23, Folder 18)
  - Parents Day, 1956-1964 (Box A23, Folder 19)
  - Parents Kick-Off Meeting, 1960 (Box A23, Folder 20)
  - Parking, 1958-1964 (Box A23, Folder 21)
  - Patents Committee, 1949-1959 (Box A23, Folder 22)
    Discontinued 9/1/59.
  - Pauling, Dr. Linus, 1961 (Box A23, Folder 23)
  - Peace Corps, 1960-1962 (Box A23, Folder 24)
  - Peace Corps, 1962-1965 (Box A23, Folder 25)
  - Permanente Cement Co., 1957-1958 (Box A23, Folder 26)
  - Philanthropic Digest, 1957-1961 (Box A23, Folder 27)
  - Pacific Gas and Electric (PG & E) Dispute, 1962-1964 (Box A23, Folder 28)
    SLAC powerlines, Woodside
  - Philippine Science Community, 1961-1962 (Box A23, Folder 29)
  - Philosophy, Dept. of, 1959-1964 (Box A23, Folder 30)
  - Pigott, Paul (Trustee), 1960-1961 (Box A23, Folder 31)
  - Pike, Thomas, 1953-1964 (Box A23, Folder 32)
  - Pitzer, Dr. - Inauguration as president of Rice Univ., 1962 (Box A23, Folder 33)
  - Placement Services, 1964-1965 (Box A23, Folder 34)
  - Planning Coordinating Committee, 1965-1966 (Box A23, Folder 35)
    Formerly Three Vice Presidents Meeting
  - Political Union, Stanford, 1958-1959 (Box A24, Folder 1)
  - Political Union, Stanford, 1959-1961 (Box A24, Folder 2)
  - Political Union, Stanford, 1961-1964 (Box A24, Folder 3)
  - Political Union, Stanford, 1958-1959 (Box A24, Folder 4)
    Speakers
  - Political Union, Stanford, 1960 (Box A24, Folder 5)
    Socialist Caucus
  - Post Office, 1961-1964 (Box A24, Folder 6)
  - Post Office - Dedication, 2/11/60, 1960 (Box A24, Folder 7)
  - Pre-Registration Program, 1957-1964 (Box A24, Folder 8)
  - Pre-Registration Program, 1964-1966 (Box A24, Folder 9)
  - President's Council, The, 1956-1958 (Box A24, Folder 10)
  - President's Courtesy List, 1957-1959 (Box A24, Folder 11)
  - President's Dinner, 1960 (Box A24, Folder 12)
    Los Angeles, 7/6/60.
  - President's Faculty Tea, 1958-1961 (Box A24, Folder 13)
  - President's Report, 1957-1964 (Box A24, Folder 14)
  - Primate Colony - Proposed, 1959-1960 (Box A24, Folder 15)
  - Private Investigators, 1962 (Box A24, Folder 16)
  - Professional Center, The Stanford, 1957-1959 (Box A24, Folder 17)
  - Provost's Staff, 1959-1965 (Box A24, Folder 18)
  - Psychology, Dept. of, 1960 (Box A24, Folder 19)
  - Public Exercises Committee, 1953-1959 (Box A24, Folder 20)
  - Public Exercises Committee, 1955-1961 (Box A24, Folder 21)
    Subcommittee on Commencement and Baccalaureate
  - Public Exercises Committee, 1957-1960 (Box A24, Folder 22)
    Subcommittee on Public Events
  - Public Exercises Committee, 1956-1959 (Box A24, Folder 23)
  - Public Exercises Committee, 1956-1957 (Box A24, Folder 24)
  - Public Exercises Committee, 1957-1959 (Box A24, Folder 25)
  - Public Exercises Committee, 1958-1959 (Box A24, Folder 26)
  - Public Exercises Committee, 1959-1960 (Box A24, Folder 27)
    including visit by Richard Nixon
  - Public Exercises Committee, 1960-1961 (Box A24, Folder 28)
  - Public Exercises Committee, 1960-1961 (Box A24, Folder 29)
  - Public Exercises Committee, 1961-1962 (Box A24, Folder 30)
  - Public Exercises Committee, 1961-1963 (Box A24, Folder 31)
  - Public Exercises - Fred Glovers File, 1962-1963 (Box A24, Folder 32)
  - Public Exercises, 1963-1965 (Box A24, Folder 33)
  - Public Health Committee, 1955-1960 (Box A24, Folder 34)
  - University Publications Committee, 1954-1960 (Box A24, Folder 35)
  - Publications Committee (Budget), 1955-1956 (Box A24, Folder 36)
  - The Stanford Quad, 1955-1965 (Box A25, Folder 1)
  - Questionnaires - General, 1956-1958 (Box A25, Folder 2)
  - Questionnaires - General, 1958-1960 (Box A25, Folder 3)
  - Questionnaires - General, 1960-1962 (Box A25, Folder 4)
  - Questionnaires - General, 1962-1964 (Box A25, Folder 5)
  - Questionnaires - General, 1964-1965 (Box A25, Folder 6)
  - Questionnaires - General, 1966 (Box A25, Folder 7)
  - General "R", 1959-1964 (Box A25, Folder 8)
  - General "R", 1960-1963 (Box A25, Folder 9)
  - Radio and Television Committee, 1953-1959 (Box A25, Folder 10)
  - Radio and Television Committee, 1957-1960 (Box A25, Folder 11)
  - Radio and Television Committee, 1959-1960 (Box A25, Folder 12)
    Film Production Unit
  - Radlin, Myron L., 1960-1961 (Box A25, Folder 13)
  - Ram' s Head, 1958-1964 (Box A25, Folder 14)
  - Bay Area Rapid Transit System (BART), 1960-1961 (Box A25, Folder 15)
  - Recommendation Letters - General, 1959-1964 (Box A26, Folder 1)
    Reference letters written by Sterling for students, faculty, etc.
  - Recruiting - Faculty, 1964 (Box A26, Folder 2)
  - Registration and Academic Standing Committee, 1953-1959 (Box A26, Folder 3)
  - Religion, 1963-1964 (Box A26, Folder 4)
  - Remedial English Program - Ad Hoc Committee on, 1957-1958 (Box A26, Folder 5)
  - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) - all units, 1959-1965 (Box A26, Folder 6)
  - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) - all units, 1955-1960 (Box A26, Folder 7)
  - Report from the Campus, 1962-1963 (Box A26, Folder 8)
    Bulletin of events, speakers, clippings
  - Research in the Social Sciences, Committee on (CRISS), 1954-1958 (Box A26, Folder 9)
  - Reynolds, Ralph (Big Jim), 1955-1963 (Box A26, Folder 10)
    Letters on football and communism at Stanford
  - Robbins Committee, 1962 (Box A26, Folder 11)
    Committee on Higher Education in the United Kingdom
  - Robbins Committee, 1962 (Box A26, Folder 12)
  - Rosco Maples Pavilion, 1966 (Box A26, Folder 13)
  - Russell, Mr. Donal J. (Trustee), 1961-1964 (Box A26, Folder 14)
  - Russian Exchange Program, 1964 (Box A26, Folder 15)
    U.S. State Dept. East-West Contract
  - Russian Exchange Program, 1959-1963 (Box A26, Folder 16)
    U.S. State Dept. East-West Contract, Inter-Univ. Committee on Travel Grants
  - Russian Exchange Program, 1958-1959 (Box A26, Folder 17)
  - Russian Track Meet (Olympics), 1961-1962 (Box A26, Folder 18)
  - General "S", 1957-1960 (Box A27, Folder 1)
  - General "S", 1960-1962 (Box A27, Folder 2)
  - General "S", 1962-1964 (Box A27, Folder 3)
  - General "S", 1959-1965 (Box A27, Folder 4)
  - Sackett, Sheldon F., 1958-1959 (Box A27, Folder 5)
    Newspaper publisher
  - Sacramento Host Breakfast, 1962 (Box A27, Folder 6)
    Special Events
  - Salaries, Stanford, 1958-1960 (Box A27, Folder 7)
    Data, Academic Rank, etc.
  - Salary Data - Other Institutions, 1956-1964 (Box A27, Folder 8)
  - Salk, Jonas E. - Salk Institute, 1959-1960 (Box A27, Folder 9)
  - San Francisco Board of Education, 1959-1960 (Box A27, Folder 10)
    Curriculum Survey
  - San Francisco, City of, 1960-1964 (Box A27, Folder 11)
    Including clubs, associations, newspapers, etc.
  - San Francisco General Hospital, 1956-1959 (Box A27, Folder 12)
  - San Francisco Social Hygiene and Health Assoc., 1957-1960 (Box A27, Folder 13)
  - Santa Clara County Medical Society, 1957-1958 (Box A27, Folder 14)
  - Saturday Evening POst, 1960-1963 (Box A27, Folder 15)
  - Sauhering, William Jr., 1955-1960 (Box A27, Folder 16)
    Earlier corresp. filed "W.R. Coe" 1955-1956 General
  - Schedule and Examinations Committee, 1954-1960 (Box A27, Folder 17)
  - Schools - General, 1957-1964 (Box A27, Folder 18)
  - Science Advisory Boards - Public, 1961 (Box A27, Folder 19)
  - Selective Service System, 1956-1962 (Box A27, Folder 20)
  - Selective Service, 1965-1966 (Box A27, Folder 21)
  - Senior Research Associates, 1957-1960 (Box A27, Folder 22)
  - Seven University Group, 1958-1959 (Box A27, Folder 23)
  - Shakespeare Festival, 1965 (Box A27, Folder 24)
  - Sierra Camp, Alumni Association, 1953-1960 (Box A27, Folder 25)
  - Sloan Dedication, 12/11/64, 1964 (Box A27, Folder 26)
  - Smog, University Committee on, 1957-1958 (Box A27, Folder 27)
  - Southern Pacific Program, 1955-1956 (Box A27, Folder 28)
  - Space, Academic, 1951-1952 (Box A28, Folder 1)
  - Space Activities (Outer Space), 1961 (Box A28, Folder 2)
  - Space Administration, Academic, 1960-1962 (Box A28, Folder 3)
  - Space Administration, Academic, 1962-1964 (Box A28, Folder 4)
  - Space Engineering Building, 1967 (Box A28, Folder 5)
    Groundbreaking, 6/16/67
  - Space Engineering Building - Trustees Invitation, 1967 (Box A28, Folder 6)
  - Space Utilization, Study of, 1958-1959 (Box A28, Folder 7)
    see also Classroom Scheduling and Utilization Committee, 1959-1960
  - Spaght, Monroe E (Trustee), 1955-1956 (Box A28, Folder 8)
    President of Shell Oil Co.
  - Spalding Organ, 1951-1961 (Box A28, Folder 9)
  - Special Students, 1961-1966 (Box A28, Folder 10)
    Grades, etc. for children of "nationally prominent figures."
  - Sports Illustrated, 1958-1964 (Box A28, Folder 11)
  - Staff Handbook, 1963 (Box A28, Folder 12)
  - Staff Meetings, 1959-1962 (Box A28, Folder 13)
  - Standard Oil of California, 1956-1963 (Box A28, Folder 14)
    Includes faculty seminars
  - Stanford Associates, 1957-1958 (Box A28, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Associates, 1958-1964 (Box A28, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Associates, 1964-1965 (Box A28, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Associates, 1965 (Box A28, Folder 18)
    George Ditz, Uncommon Man Award, 11/30/65
  - Stanford Associates - Advertising campaign, 1956-1958 (Box A28, Folder 19)
    Stanford Story
  - Stanford Associates, 1958-1959 (Box A28, Folder 20)
    Corporations Committee
  - Stanford Associates, 1959-1960 (Box A28, Folder 21)
    Corporations Committee, includes corporate reminders
  - Stanford Associates, 1966 (Box A28, Folder 22)
    Dinner, 1/20/66.
  - Stanford Associates, 1958-1959 (Box A28, Folder 23)
    Parents Committee
  - Stanford Associates, 1954-1959 (Box A28, Folder 24)
    "R" Planners, Louis Roseberry plan
  - Stanford Associates, 1958-1959 (Box A28, Folder 25)
    Stanford Fund
  - Stanford Associates, 1959-1960 (Box A28, Folder 26)
    Stanford Fund Committees
  - Stanford Associates, 1957-1960 (Box A28, Folder 27)
    Stanford Fund - Class Solicitation
  - Stanford Associates, 1957 (Box A28, Folder 28)
    The Stanford Story
  - Corporate Gifts Committee for Stanford, 1956-1958 (Box A28, Folder 29)
  - Stanford Electronics Laboratories, 1956-1957 (Box A28, Folder 30)
  - Stanford Electronics Laboratories, 1957-1958 (Box A28, Folder 31)
  - Stanford Daily, 1955-1962 (Box A28, Folder 32)
  - Stanford Deadly, The, 1966 (Box A28, Folder 33)
    Student newspaper
  - San Francisco Hospitals - Letters regarding use of, 1958-1959 (Box A28, Folder 34)
  - Stanford in Austria - Dedication, 1965 Nov 4 (Box A29, Folder 1)
  - Stanford in France, Italy - Dedications, 1960 Oct 8 (Box A29, Folder 2)
  - Stanford in Germany Opening, 1958 Jun 24 (Box A29, Folder 3)
  - Stanford in Germany, 1957-1958 (Box A29, Folder 4)
  - Stanford in Germany, 1958-1959 (Box A29, Folder 5)
  - Stanford in Germany, 1959-1962 (Box A29, Folder 6)
  - Stanford in Harlaxton, Britain - Dedication, 1966 Apr 16 (Box A29, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Land Development, 1960 (Box A29, Folder 8)
    Letters pro and con regarding foothill industrial development
  - Stanford Land Development, 1956-1958 (Box A29, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Land Development, 1958-1961 (Box A29, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Land Development, 1960 (Box A29, Folder 11)
    Foothill industry
  - Stanford Land Development, 1961-1963 (Box A29, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Land Development, 1960 (Box A29, Folder 13)
    Open house and meeting at Bowman House, 4/2/60
  - Stanford Law Review, 1962 (Box A29, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center Program (SLAC), 1961-1963 (Box A29, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center Program (SLAC), 1956-1963 (Box A29, Folder 16)
    Scientific Policy Committee
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center Program (SLAC), 1964 (Box A29, Folder 17)
    NLRB Hearing, 12/2/64
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center Program (SLAC), 1963-1966 (Box A29, Folder 18)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center Program (SLAC), 1963-1966 (Box A29, Folder 19)
  - Stanford Mausoleum, Memorial Monuments, 1963 (Box A29, Folder 20)
  - Stanford Move - Winds of Freedom, 1957-1959 (Box A29, Folder 21)
  - Stanford Overseas Program, 1960-1961 (Box A29, Folder 22)
  - Stanford in Washington, 1963-1964 (Box A29, Folder 23)
    Dept. of State Summer Intern Program
  - Stanford Petroleum Investment Committee, 1955-1956 (Box A29, Folder 24)
  - Stanford Hospital in San Francisco, 1956-1959 (Box A29, Folder 35)
  - Stanford Hospital in San Francisco, 1956-1958 (Box A29, Folder 36)
    Auxiliary
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 1965 (Box A30, Folder 1)
    Joint Committee of Stanford U. and SRI. 1st meeting 3/5/65.
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 1965-196 (Box A30, Folder 2)
    Annual Meeting
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 1957-1963 (Box A30, Folder 3)
    Board Action, Re-election of members
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 1965-1966 (Box A30, Folder 4)
    Executive Committee
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 1963-1965 (Box A30, Folder 5)
    Executive Committee (reconstituted 3/63)
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 1965 (Box A30, Folder 6)
    Financial Statements
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 1962 (Box A30, Folder 7)
    Advisory Council
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 1961 (Box A30, Folder 8)
    International Business Conference, 9/11/61
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 1959-1962 (Box A30, Folder 9)
    International Business Conference Letters
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 1961-1963 (Box A30, Folder 10)
    International Committee
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 1964-1965 (Box A30, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 1961 (Box A30, Folder 12)
    International Industry Conference, Sterling Reception, 9/10/61
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 1962-1965 (Box A30, Folder 13)
    National Industrial Conference Board
  - Stanford Rest Homes, 1961-1962 (Box A30, Folder 14)
    see also Alpine House after 9/62
  - Stanford Shopping Center, 1954-1966 (Box A30, Folder 15)
    Sales Volume Comparison
  - Stanford Ski Club, 1961 (Box A30, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Today, 1957-1960 (Box A30, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Today (New), 1960-1966 (Box A30, Folder 18)
    Includes Editorial Advisory Committee
  - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, 1954-1957 (Box A30, Folder 19)
  - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, 1958-1961 (Box A30, Folder 20)
    Including speech materials 1962-1963
  - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, 1963-1966 (Box A30, Folder 21)
    see also Speech File - Annual
  - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, 1955-1960 (Box A30, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, 1957 (Box A30, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, 1958-1959 (Box A30, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, 1959-1960 (Box A30, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Union Board of Governors, 1960-1962 (Box A30, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Village, 1953-1964 (Box A30, Folder 6)
  - Stanton, Robert M., 1959-1963 (Box A31, Folder 1)
    Aris Gloves, Inc.
  - Statistics, Dept. of, 1952-1953 (Box A31, Folder 2)
  - Statistics, Dept. of, 1955-1956 (Box A31, Folder 3)
  - Statistics, Dept. of, 1956-1957 (Box A31, Folder 4)
  - Statistics, Dept. of, 1957-1958 (Box A31, Folder 5)
  - Statistics, Dept. of, 1959-1960 (Box A31, Folder 6)
  - Stauffer Building Dedication, 1961 Mar 1 (Box A31, Folder 7)
  - Stauffer Laboratory for Chemical Engineering, 1966 (Box A31, Folder 8)
    Dedication, 12/12/66
  - Stauffer Laboratory for Physical Chemistry, 1964 (Box A31, Folder 9)
    Dedication, 11/17/64
  - Stern Hall, 1949-1963 (Box A31, Folder 10)
  - Stern Hall, 1958-1959 (Box A31, Folder 11)
    Addition Dedication, 3/4/59. Includes origninal dedication, 1950
  - Sterling, J.E.W - 10th Anniversary Celebration, 1959 (Box A31, Folder 12)
    10/31/59
  - Sterling - Publicity, Clippings, 1949-1971 (Box A31, Folder 13)
  - Sterling - 15th Anniversary Dinner, 1964 Oct 10 (Box A31, Folder 14)
  - Sterling - Board of Trustees Dinner, 1959 Dec 17 (Box A31, Folder 15)
  - Sterling - Honorary Degree from UC Berkeley, 1958 (Box A31, Folder 16)
  - Sterling Luncheon - Hoover Advisory Board, 1959 (Box A31, Folder 17)
    8/3/59
  - Storke Student Publications Building, 1963-1964 (Box A31, Folder 18)
    Site Dedication, 11/20/64
  - Strucinski, Mitchell, 1960-1961 (Box A31, Folder 19)
    Prison inmate admitted to Stegners Creative Writing Program. Later theft of library material.
  - Student Advisory Committee on Academic Affairs, 1958-1960 (Box A31, Folder 20)
  - Student Advisory Committee on Academic Affairs, 1958-1960 (Box A31, Folder 21)
  - Student Affairs and Services, Committe on, 1960-1965 (Box A31, Folder 22)
  - Student Employment, Final Report on, 1957 (Box A31, Folder 23)
  - Student Leaders, Meetings with, 1962-1963 (Box A31, Folder 24)
  - Student Leaders, Meetings with, 1963-1964 (Box A31, Folder 25)
    Student Advisory Committee
  - Student Leaders, Meetings with, 1964-1965 (Box A31, Folder 26)
  - Student Leaders, Meetings with, 1965-1966 (Box A31, Folder 27)
  - Student Residences, Committee on, 1958-1960 (Box A31, Folder 28)
  - Summer Festival - 20th Century Innovations, 1966 (Box A31, Folder 29)
  - Summer Quarter Committee, 1953-1959 (Box A31, Folder 30)
  - Summer Quarter, 1956-1957 (Box A31, Folder 31)
  - Summer Quarter (Budget), 1957-1958 (Box A31, Folder 32)
  - Summer Quarter, 1958-1959 (Box A31, Folder 33)
  - Summer Session, 1957-1958 (Box A31, Folder 34)
  - Summer Session, 1959-1962 (Box A31, Folder 35)
  - Summer Session, 1959-1964 (Box A31, Folder 36)
  - Supplementary Research Grants Committee, 1951-1958 (Box A31, Folder 37)
  - Surveys and Studies - Misc., 1963-1968 (Box A31, Folder 38)
  - Swain Library of Chemistry - Dedication, 1962 Apr 16 (Box A31, Folder 39)
  - Syntex Dedication, 1967 Mar 1 (Box A31, Folder 40)
  - General "T", 1957-1960 (Box A32, Folder 1)
  - General "T", 1960-1965 (Box A32, Folder 2)
  - Taylor, Edward DeWitt, 1946-1958 (Box A32, Folder 3)
    Typographical Library
  - Teacher Education, Committee on, 1959 (Box A32, Folder 4)
  - Teach-In, 1965 May 17 (Box A32, Folder 5)
    Viet Nam, clippings
  - Television and Radio, 1956-1960 (Box A32, Folder 6)
  - Television and Radio, 1960-1961 (Box A32, Folder 7)
  - Terman, Frederick E., 1957-1965 (Box A32, Folder 8)
  - J. Walter Thompson Co., 1958-1959 (Box A32, Folder 9)
    Medical School, Public Relations
  - Time, Inc., 1959-1964 (Box A32, Folder 10)
  - Tokyo Center Dedication, 4/12/61, 1961 (Box A32, Folder 11)
  - Topping, Dr. Norman, 1958 (Box A32, Folder 12)
    USC Dinner, 11/10/58
  - Traffic and Parking Committee, 1956-1959 (Box A32, Folder 13)
    Winbigler, Chairman
  - Travel (includes Council on Student Travel), 1956-1965 (Box A32, Folder 14)
    Travel Schedules
  - Tresidder Memorial Concert, 4/8/56, 1956 (Box A32, Folder 15)
  - Tresidder Memorial Union, 1960-1963 (Box A32, Folder 16)
  - Tresidder Union Site Dedication, 1961 (Box A32, Folder 17)
    7/20/61
  - Tresidder Memorial Union Dedication, 1962 (Box A32, Folder 18)
    9/29/62
  - Trustees - Academic Affairs Committee, 1956-1960 (Box A32, Folder 19)
  - Trustees - Academic Affairs Committee, 1960-1966 (Box A32, Folder 20)
  - Trustees - Members of the Board, 1953-1960 (Box A32, Folder 21)
  - Trustees, 1957-1958 (Box A32, Folder 22)
  - Trustees, 1958-1960 (Box A32, Folder 23)
  - Trustees, 1960-1962 (Box A32, Folder 24)
  - Trustees, 1963-1964 (Box A32, Folder 25)
  - Trustees - Meeting in Los Angeles, 1959 Jan 15 (Box A32, Folder 26)
  - Trustees - Meetings, 1960-1963 (Box A32, Folder 27)
  - Trustees - Agendas, Notes and Corrections, 1960-1962 (Box A32, Folder 28)
  - Trustees - Agendas, Notes and Corrections, 1962-1966 (Box A32, Folder 29)
  - Trustees - Meeting in Los Angeles, 1961 Jan 19 (Box A32, Folder 30)
  - Trustees - Meeting in Los Angeles, 1962 Feb 15 (Box A32, Folder 31)
  - Trustees - Additional Matters, 1962-1966 (Box A32, Folder 32)
  - Trustees - Meeting in Los Angeles, 1966 Jan 20 (Box A32, Folder 33)
  - Trustees - Agendas, Notes and Corrections, 1959-1960 (Box A32, Folder 34)
  - Trustees - Budget Committee, 1959-1962 (Box A33, Folder 1)
  - Trustees - Building and Grounds Committee, 1956-1958 (Box A33, Folder 2)
  - Trustees - Building and Grounds Committee, 1958-1959 (Box A33, Folder 3)
  - Trustees - Building and Grounds Committee, 1959-1960 (Box A33, Folder 4)
  - Trustees - Building and Grounds Committee, 1960-1966 (Box A33, Folder 5)
  - Trustees - Campaign Steering Committee, 1963-1964 (Box A33, Folder 6)
  - Trustees - Committees, misc., 1960-1962 (Box A33, Folder 7)
  - Trustees - Campus Board Meeting, 1957-1965 (Box A33, Folder 8)
  - Trustees - Campus Events, Monthly Reports, 1961-1962 (Box A33, Folder 9)
  - Trustees - Trustees/Associates Dinner, 1960-1961 (Box A33, Folder 10)
    Los Angeles, 1/19/61
  - Trustees - Special Committee on Exterior Architecture and Landscaping, 1955-1959 (Box A33, Folder 11)
  - Trustees - Development Steering Committee, 1958-1961 (Box A33, Folder 12)
  - Trustees - Finance Committee, 1956-1963 (Box A33, Folder 13)
  - Trustees - Special Meeting, 1959 (Box A33, Folder 14)
    Joint Committee on Finance and P & D
  - Trustees - Board of Governors Stanford Hospitals, 1956-1957 (Box A33, Folder 15)
  - Trustees - Board of Governors Stanford Hospitals, 1957-1958 (Box A33, Folder 16)
  - Trustees - Hoover Institution Committee, 1958-1960 (Box A33, Folder 17)
    Reprocessed 10/88. See Hoover Series.